I have an iron will.
我有鋼鐵般的意志。
to achieve the goals of a peaceful revolution
達成和平改革的目標
to achieve the goals of a civil nation
成為公民主義的國家
My house is small.
我的房子很小。
It can be hard to breathe.
在裡面很難呼吸。
So when I found that key,
當我找到這個鑰匙。
I was curious.
我很好奇。
Because I knew the key belonged to the big man
因為我知道這個鑰匙是屬於一個大男人的
I knew it was for his big house.
我知道是他大房子的。
I heard he was gone.
我聽說他不見了。
And it was true. He was gone.
是真的。他不見了。
The house was empty.
房子是空的。
So I took a chance.
所以我逮到機會。
You would've done the same.
你也會做同樣的事。
Let me tell you.
讓我告訴你。
It's a different world inside.
裡面是不同的世界。
He's got everything he needs.
他擁有所有他所需要的的東西。
And more
及更多的
So why shouldn't he share?
那他幹嘛不分享?
Can't he give me a little?
他不能給我一點嗎?
Aren't I a good kid?
我不是乖小孩嗎?
I deserve it.
我應該得到啊。
With all that space, I could breathe.
有這些空間，我可以呼吸。
I felt like I could move.
我覺得我可以隨意走動。
I felt like I could fly.
我覺得我可以飛。
Who's there?
誰在那裡?
There he is!
他在這!
Get out!
走開!
But that's not my house.
但這不是我的房子。
And it never will be.
且永遠不是。
So where do I go?
那我該去哪裡?
Where can I breathe?
哪裡我可以呼吸?
I guess...
我想...
there are other rooms.
還有其他的房間。